{
    "subject": "resource/Gundakar,_Prince_of_Liechtenstein",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/isPrimaryTopicOf",
    "object": "http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gundakar,_Prince_of_Liechtenstein",
    "human_readable": "Gundakar, Prince of Liechtenstein is the primary topic of Wikipedia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9450436234474182,
            "question": "What is the primary topic of Wikipedia about Gundakar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8779433369636536,
            "question": "Who is Gundakar, Prince of Liechtenstein?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7997872829437256,
            "question": "What is the significance of Gundakar in Liechtenstein's history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7423934936523438,
            "question": "Is Gundakar a prince?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.716977059841156,
            "question": "How popular is the Wikipedia article about Gundakar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5274906158447266,
            "question": "Are there any notable images or videos related to Gundakar on Wikipedia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48289263248443604,
            "question": "What are some key events or achievements associated with Gundakar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41496405005455017,
            "question": "What is the name of the principality that Gundakar rules?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.399922639131546,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Gundakar's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3755095899105072,
            "question": "To what country does Gundakar belong?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Gundakar, Prince of Liechtenstein is the primary topic of Wikipedia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2289_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about Gundakar's family?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2289_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the principality that Gundakar rules?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2289_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some key events or achievements associated with Gundakar?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2289_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2289_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2289_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2289_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2289_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2289_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2289_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2289_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2289_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2289_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2289_73.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After reviewing the context information, I found that:\n\n* There are multiple documents related to a person named Gundakar, but they seem to refer to different individuals.\n* One document (path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2289/re-ranker-msmarco/2.txt) is about a Prince of Liechtenstein named Gundakar, who was born in 1580 and died in 1658.\n* Another document (path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2289/re-ranker-msmarco/30.txt) is about a Prince Gundakar Albert Alfred Petrus of Liechtenstein, who was born in 1949 and is still alive.\n\nGiven this information, I would say that the triple \"Gundakar, Prince of Liechtenstein is the primary topic of Wikipedia\" does not have enough evidence to support it as \"yes\". There are multiple individuals with similar names, and without more context, it's unclear which one is being referred to. Therefore:\n\n`{'output': 'no'}`"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Gundakar, Prince of Liechtenstein, including his birth date, place, and some biographical details. The presence of articles like \"Princess Gundakar of Liechtenstein / From Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia\" strongly supports the assertion that he is a primary topic of Wikipedia."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The primary topic of Wikipedia seems to be \"Princess Gundakar of Liechtenstein\", not Gundakar, Prince of Liechtenstein.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}